What is this?
What in the world happened here?
Perfect.
Team, watch out!
You've been giving us a hard time.
Power incompatible with humans destroys the physical body.
To recover using that incompatible power only to use it again?
That is how far Shido is willing to go.
If it means seeing Touka, he'll do whatever it takes.
Thank you.
Where is Touka?
Where is she?
Tell me.
What a truly pitiful sight.
Oh.
Gabriel. Solo.
Miku?
How dare you refer to me so casually?
I only let my closest friends call me Miku,
and I don't see a rude klutz like you making that list.
What do you want us to do?
Should we come inside and help with the rescue mission?
No, thank you.
There's so many of you.
If you all came, they'd likely hear us from a mile away.
Why don't you stay outside and make sure those pesky wizards
stay off our tails while we save you-know-who?
Miku, what are you doing here?
Wait a sec.
Is this about that promise?
Don't go getting the wrong idea, you primate.
I wouldn't dream of letting you seal my powers, promise or not.
I didn't come here for you.
I came for the sole purpose of adding another spirit to my collection,
so don't go thinking we're partners.
Either way, thank you.
I owe you one.
Now die!
Oh no, she's completely lost it.
You're right!
Doesn't look like she's in any state to make decisions right now.
It's likely her mind was forced to process too much magical power in too short a time.
Mana!
Don't worry.
We're on our way!
You dodged.
That wasn't bad at all.
I'm actually impressed.
Mana!
Perfect.
Two on one.
Be gone!
Blast off!
Normally, I don't like ganging up two against one,
but if that's the way Ike wants it, then so be it.
Mana!
Hey, Mana!
How does it feel now that I've got you cornered?
Tell me!
Your reflexes are impressive.
However...
Did you see that?
That's what I call a jackpot!
Sergeant Tomiichi!
You're right on time.
Where's Shido?
Don't worry about Shido.
He's perfectly safe.
He's in building number one right now.
You're gonna have to go through me.
I'll be happy to.
Well, you're the prettiest one yet.
I'm looking for my friend Toka.
Be a dear and tell me where you're keeping her.
Uh, sorry.
That's classified information.
If you don't tell, I'll hate you.
I'll have no choice but to hate you forever.
No!
Please!
Anything but that!
Your friend is quarantined on the 18th floor.
If you use this ID, you'll be able to get in.
Just don't hate me forever.
I would die.
Like, seriously.
You're sweet.
You see, now that wasn't so terrible, was it?
Like they say, there's more than one way to skin a cat.
You're freaking me out.
She said the quarantine area was on the 18th floor.
Right?
Let's go, Miku.
Would you please stop acting like we're working together on this mission?
And it grosses me out.
Team, fire at will!
Do you think an attack like that is enough to stop someone as powerful as me?
I really do hate being underestimated.
What's wrong?
Do you know how pathetic you look?
If you keep pushing yourself like this, you'll burn out.
I told you already.
I'm willing to do whatever it takes to save Toka.
And I don't have time to waste.
Oh, yeah, sure.
You're a big loser, you know that?
Are you that enthralled with the idea of rescuing the tragic heroine?
I know you think you're some kind of superhero, Shido, but you're not.
Now that you're confronted with the reality of the situation,
do you want to take back what you said about Toka being more important than your own life?
You can tell the truth.
It won't make me more disappointed in you.
When I ask you a question, I expect an answer.
Hmm.
Ooh, I've got a great idea.
Why don't you drop the whole hero act and just give up on saving Toka?
It's smart.
We could leave this place right now and won't have to worry about dying at the hands of a...
Will you shut up?
Nobody can ever replace Toka.
Please, we both know you can't keep this act up forever.
That's all this rescue mission really is in the first place, isn't it?
One big show.
You've got the wrong idea.
Why do you always think the worst of humans?
Just shut up!
Humans are nothing but toys for my amusement.
The men are my slaves, and the girls are my pretty little playthings.
That's all humans are worth, and let me tell you, it isn't much.
Miku, I don't understand.
Why do you hate men so much?
And why do you treat people like they're nothing but objects?
What happened to you that made you see humans this way?
Isn't the answer to your question obvious?
It's just the way you people are.
But weren't you a human once?
Before phantom or noise or whatever turns you, you were just a girl, a run-of-the-mill human being no different than me, weren't you?
Am I wrong?
It's true.
But how did you know that?
Let's just say an acquaintance of mine told me.
Yod's power is recollection.
A powerful technique that gives me a special inside look into some of the target's recent memories.
If you're a human being too, Miku, does that mean you hate yourself?
It would be much better if you'd shut your mouth, jerk!
What do you know about it anyway?
You don't know me at all!
You're right.
But maybe if you talk to me, I can help you.
Miku!
Alright, fine, you win.
I'm human.
Or, I guess you could say I was.
I was a normal little girl who loves singing more than anything.
My name was Tsukino Yoimachi.
My songs were all I had growing up, and when I was able to make a career out of singing and reach so many people with my music, I was as happy as I'd ever been.
Everyone loved my songs, which gave me great joy.
I was thrilled to share it with my fans.
But one day, after my first album dropped, my manager set me up with a producer.
He was from a TV station, so it seemed like a decent opportunity.
My manager told me to be extra nice.
Hold on, extra nice? Does that mean...
Yes, I'm afraid it means what you think.
I refused him, of course.
I didn't want to be a TV star anyway.
I just wanted to make music for myself and the people who loved it.
But then a scandal about the producer in me was published in a weekly magazine.
No one, not even my agency, was there to protect me.
You know what hurt me the most?
My fans.
No, the brutal reactions of the people I thought were my fans was the worst.
I tried to take comfort in my music.
As long as they listened to it, I thought they would come around.
But...
The stress became too much, and I lost my voice forever.
So you see, I stood up for myself, my pride.
And thanks to those evil men, my voice was gone.
I think what happened to you was a terrible thing.
The fact that your agents and your fans turned their backs on you makes me angry.
But even so, you can't blame the entire human race for that.
What do you know about it?
You men are all pigs!
Trust me, Miku, there are plenty of people out there who would love to listen to your music.
I bet you have droves of fans.
And I bet they don't care about some stupid made-up scandal.
No, you're wrong.
I'm not.
But you'll never find out, because you've made human beings your boogeyman, so you don't have to face your fears.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
I'm sick of listening to your crap!
Idiot!
Moron!
Stupid head!
Miku, calm down.
You're just mad because you know I'm right.
Nope, wrong again.
I'm mad because you're a complete jackass, you stupid, stupid man!
You're so annoying.
Damn it.
I can't leave Yoshino, Kaguya, or Yuzuru to you after all, can I?
I'm definitely sealing your spirit powers after this.
Are you trying to tell me to go back to how I was?
There we are!
Come on!
You're just a mute, hopeless, sat in a row?
No, I didn't say that!
Don't you get it?
I want you to conquer your fears and sing with your real voice instead of hiding behind this one and controlling people.
Stop talking like you know everything about me!
As long as I can use this voice to control people, I can be the best idol there is.
Without this power, who would choose to listen to me?
You don't get it, do you?
I'm nothing without this!
I would listen to you, Miku!
I did listen.
It was only one song.
But it was good, and you gave it your all.
I heard your passion.
You lie.
I don't believe you, Shido, not one bit.
When I was being dragged through the gutter and a single fan came to my defense, I was all alone.
My back was against the wall and no one came to help.
Well, I'm here now, Miku.
And I know there are tons of fans out there like me who will do the same.
Miku, if you're right when you say you have nothing without your power, just know at the very least you'll have me.
Well, thanks, but I know you'll break your promise.
I won't believe your lies!
You know what?
You need to learn to trust people.
Leave me alone!
If you would just give them a chance, you might find out that...
I can't hear you!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Well, I'm pretty sure this is it.
Hold on, Toka.
We'll have you back soon.
Origami Tobiichi.
I must admit, I didn't expect to see you here today.
You're brave, but considering that mishmash of equipment you're carrying, you're also quite foolish.
It's equipment from a terrorist group we uncovered.
There's no ID restriction on it.
This is the only place that escaped HQ's retrieval order.
Please know that I say this out of concern.
If I were you, I'd tread carefully.
Or you'll die today.
If I can save Shido, it'll be worth it.
So you do whatever you have to do!
If you think an attack like that is going to work, then you're more foolish than I thought.
I've been underestimated.
I can't see!
You've thought this through.
Instead of going after the territory, you aim to confuse the mind that generates it.
Interesting.
However, it's quite crude, not elegant at all.
But it could work.
Of course, in order for it to work, you'd have to be fighting someone besides me.
I hate to break it to you, but unfortunately, this isn't something you can use against the world's strongest wizard.
I'd hate to kill Ike's favor, but I don't have another choice.
Besides, you'd do the same to me, wouldn't you?
Time to say goodnight, Sergeant Tobeichi.
What's happening?
Converging magic power cannon missile tank.
Target Ellen Mathers.
Direct hit confirmed.
If it was required of me, I do believe I could hit an apple right off the top of someone's head blindfolded.
Now you've really upset me.
Congratulations, Miss Tobeichi.
After countless confrontations, you're only the second person to ever successfully injure me.
I've got to hand it to you.
You're indeed a powerful wizard.
You should be extremely proud of yourself right now.
It's too bad.
Because now, you die.
It's Ike.
Where is he?
My time here is up.
Lucky you.
Bye-bye.
Tobeichi.
I've been waiting for you.
May I call you a friend of the princess?
That seems like a safe assumption.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Allow me to officially introduce myself.
Isaac Westcott, D.E.M. Industries.
Isaac Westcott?
I know that name.
Good job making it here alive.
D.Va.
You as well.
What are you?
Wait.
Don't tell me.
You can't be.
There's no way.
I'm a human and my name's Shido.
I've come to save Toka.
If you know what's good for you, you'll get her out of there.
So you're Shido Itsuka?
Amazing.
I never thought I'd meet someone who could handle the power of the spirits.
I didn't think it was possible, but apparently I was wrong.
How incredibly funny this is.
And every single detail is going precisely according to that woman's plan.
So now do you see what I was talking about?
This is exactly why I don't like men.
I don't like him either, but it's not because he's a man.
Let her out or else, Westcott!
And if I were to say no, I wonder, what would you do then?
I should probably be afraid, right?
If you don't let her go willingly, I'll have to make you do it!
And how would you do that exactly?
I'm very curious.
This is your last chance.
Let Toka go.
Now!
Don't worry.
I won't fight.
I'm not nearly as skillful as my counterpart, Ellen.
Are you all right?
Who's there?
It's me!
Shido?
Shido!
I'm here.
Don't worry, Toka.
I'm sorry you took so long.
Let her go.
Open this now!
You can control the power of spirits, can you not?
Why don't you cut it and tear it open yourself?
Miku, I need him to do what I say.
Can you help me?
I suppose.
Though honestly, I really don't like you telling me what to do.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
There's something important I need to tell you, Shido Itsuka.
If you keep standing where you are right now, you'll be in danger.
Wait!
Shido!
No!
Ellen!
Nothing personal.
It's my duty to break any sword pointed at Ike.
Shido!
I attacked because he summoned an angel.
I believed you were in danger.
I hope that's all right, Ike.
It's fine.
And come to think of it, it's more than fine.
It works out better this way.
Get up!
Don't.
Shido!
Come on!
Get up!
You can't leave me!
I would save my breath, spirit princess.
There's no hope for Shido now.
I'm going to make you watch me take his life.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid there's nothing you can do.
Although, it would be interesting to watch you try and stop Ellen's blade with everything you have.
Spirit armor, your angel.
Beyond that, well, I suppose we'll find out what happens.
I truly can't wait to see the result, princess.
Santa!
I won't let you do that!
Don't worry!
I'll save you!
I won't let you die!
I don't care what happens to me, I swear!
Use whatever you do!
Please, don't hurt Shido!
Please!
I'll do anything you say!
Just don't hurt him!
Take anything you want, please.
Break my heart.
Rip it in two.
But not Shido.
Not him.
You can't.
I don't care what you do.
Just promise me.
Swear to me that you'll spare his life.
Please, don't do this.
I beg you!
No!
Shido!
This doesn't make sense!
Levels are spiking!
Shiizaki!
What's happening?
Ma'am, we're at category E.
Spirit power levels are negative.
This can't be.
Sephiroth's inversion.
What is this?
It is the kingdom, Ellen.
It has inverted.
Finally!
The time is here!
The demon king has returned!
Do you remember theora's arm?
Probably not.
A tale has governed.
A tale of anger.
Inspiring.
When the greater volume has been passed.
Let's see your fate.
Vibe.
We will beeading.
You won't be state.
We must proceed.
Anyway.
I think it's all.
Thank you.
闇の手を振り払い 君の手を握る
今だって夢だって剣を手に
君のこと見つけるよ闇を裂いて
倒れたって暗くたって負けないから
この手をギュッと捕まえて
消えない雪の炎が
都会照らしている
燃alth環境にメ anymore
燃德回事
駅も少しkidsが見つ career
全 eleも裂いて体操を裂いて
祝うのにяг trace